Guide to the Edward Scott-Snell papers M3007
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- Letters to Edward Scott-Snell, 1929-1946
  - ALS from Charles Holmes to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 October 31; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - ALS from Charles Holmes to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 April 21; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 January 8; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 September 4; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 September 25; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 4; 4 pages (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 12; 4 pages (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 18; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 November 3; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 December 29; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 December 10; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 December 13; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 December 15; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 December 18; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 31; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 28; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 April 24; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 14; 3 pages (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 24; 4 pages (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 28; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 August 17; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 September 7; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 September 17; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 4; 4 pages (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 8; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 9; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 15; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 21; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 September 7; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 November 4; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 January 1; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 June 26; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 October 10; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - ALS from Hedley Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - ALS from Jacqueline Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 11; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - ALS from Lauretta Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, no year December 20; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - ALS from Lauretta Hope-Nicholson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 February 8; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - TLS from Hugh Hunt to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 7; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - ACS from Derek Kahn to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - ALS from Derek Kahn to Edward Scott-Snell, no year August 15; 4 pages (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - ALS from Gwen Keating to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - TLS from Lillah Keeble to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 24; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - ALS from Lillah Keeble to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 August 7; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - ALS from Lillah Keeble to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 18; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - TLS from Lillah Keeble to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 July 15; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - ACS from Kikki Kielland to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 August 14; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - ALS from "Gug" Kolkhorst to Edward Scott-Snell, no year November 27; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - ALS from "Gug" Kolkhorst to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - ALS from "Gug" Kolkhorst to Edward Scott-Snell, no year May 30; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - ALS from "Gug" Kolkhorst to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - ALS from "Gug" Kolkhorst to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 November 16; 7 pages (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - ALS from Norman Laing to Edward Scott-Snell, 1936 December 24; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 245)
  - ALS from John Geoffrey Lawson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 27; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - ALS from John Geoffrey Lawson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 April 27; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - ALS from John Geoffrey Lawson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 9; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - ALS from George R. Lead to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 January 26; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - ALS from George R. Lead to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 January 26; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - ALS from George R. Lead to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 5; 4 pages (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - ALS from George R. Lead to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 May 26; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - ALS from George R. Lead to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 February 4; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - ACS from Tangye Lean to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - ALS from Thomas F. Lindsay to Edward Scott-Snell, no year September 19; 4 pages (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - ALS from Tom Lindsay to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - TLS from R.G. Longman to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 August 2; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - ALS from Rose Macaulay to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 7; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - ALS from Rose Macaulay to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 November 13; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - ALS from Katherine A. Mackenzie to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 June 4; 3 pages (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - ALS from John F. Macpherson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 March 24; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - ALS from John F. Macpherson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 July 16; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - ACS from John F. Macpherson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 July 16; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - ALS from John F. Macpherson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 July 24; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - ALS from John F. Macpherson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 February 17; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - ALS from John F. Macpherson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 July 4; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - ALS from John F. Macpherson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 July 27; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Card inscribed from Mrs. Marillier de Provence to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - ALS from C.H.A. Marillier de Provence to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 28; 4 pages (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - ALS from John Masefield to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - ALS from F.B. McBurdy to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 April 11; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - TLS from Wilfred Merton to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 July 4; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - TLS from Alastair W.R. Miller to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - ALS from Alastair W.R. Miller to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - ALS from Alastair W.R. Miller to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - ALS from Alastair W.R. Miller to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - ALS from May Morris to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 June 1; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - TLS from Beverley Nichols to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 Janaury 13; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - ALS from Barbara Noble to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 12 pages (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - ALS from Barbara Noble to Edward Scott-Snell, 1937 January 1; 8 pages (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - ALS from Christopher Norriss to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 February 22; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - ALS from Christopher Norriss to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 April 22; 4 pages (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - ALS from Anne Ody to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 October 19; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - ALS from Micheline Patton to Edward Scott-Snell, no year May 17; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - ALS from Micheline Patton to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - ALS from Micheline Patton to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - ALS from Micheline Patton to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - ALS from Micheline Patton to Edward Scott-Snell, no year November 10; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - ALS from Micheline Patton to Edward Scott-Snell, no year May 10; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - ALS from C. Maresco Pearce to Whitworth re: introducing him to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 26; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - ALS from C. Maresco Pearce to Edward Scott-Snell, no year February 9; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, no year January 18; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, no year November 3; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, no year December 21; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, no year March 21; 3 pages (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 26; 4 pages (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 March 2; 4 pages (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - ALS from C. Maresco to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 August 26; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 299)
  - ALS from A.W. Polland to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 20; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 300)
  - TLS from Grant Richards to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 5; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - ALS from Grant Richards to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 14; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - ALS from Sydney Gordon Roberts to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 18; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - ALS from Sydney Gordon Roberts to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 15; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - ALS from Sydney Gordon Roberts to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - ALS from Sydney Gordon Roberts to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 March 27; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - ACS from Elspeth, Agnes & Babs Robertson to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 December 25; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - ACS from Mrs. Rodger-Cunlife to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 January 31; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - ALS from H. Lionel Rogers to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 21; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - ALS from H. Lionel Rogers to Edward Scott-Snell, 1934 July 27; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - ALS from Wilfrid Rooke-Ley to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 February 26; 2 pages (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - ALS from Wilfird Rooke-Ley to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 July 15; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - ALS from Wilfrid Rooke-Ley to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 April 27; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - ALS from Aubrey Ross to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - ALS from Albert Rutherston to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February; 1 page (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - ALS from Michael E. Sadler to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 October 13; 1 page (Box 5, Folder 316)
  - ALS from Michael E. Sadler to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 1; 1 page (Box 5, Folder 317)
  - ALS from Michael E. Sadler to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 19; 1 page (Box 5, Folder 318)
  - ALS from Annette K. Scott to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 5, Folder 319)
  - ALS from Annette K. Scott to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 320)
  - ALS from Annette K. Scott to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 321)
  - ALS from Annette K. Scott to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 322)
  - ALS from Annette K. Scott to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 323)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 324)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 5, Folder 325)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 5, Folder 326)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 327)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 328)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 5, Folder 329)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 5, Folder 330)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 331)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 7 pages (Box 5, Folder 332)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 333)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 334)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 335)
  - APS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 November 16; 1 page (Box 5, Folder 336)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 337)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 338)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 5, Folder 339)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 340)
  - ALU from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 5, Folder 341)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 345)
  - ALU from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 5, Folder 346)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 348)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 5 pages (Box 5, Folder 349)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 352)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 353)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 5, Folder 354)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 355)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 8 pages (Box 5, Folder 356)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 357)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 357)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 358)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 359)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 5, Folder 360)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 362)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 363)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 364)
  - ACS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 November 25; 1 page (Box 5, Folder 365)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 366)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 367)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 368)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 5, Folder 369)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 370)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 371)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 372)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 373)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 374)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 5, Folder 375)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 376)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 377)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 378)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 379)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 380)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 382)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 383)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 5, Folder 384)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 385)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 386)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 387)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 389)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 390)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 391)
  - ACS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, no year September 5; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 392)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 393)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 394)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 395)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 396)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 397)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 398)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 399)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 400)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 401)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 402)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 403)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 404)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 405)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 8 pages (Box 6, Folder 406)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 407)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 408)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 409)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 410)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 4 pages (Box 6, Folder 411)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 412)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 413)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 6, Folder 414)
  - ALS from Margaret Scott-Snell to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 415)
  - TLS from Martin Secker to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 March 11; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 416)
  - ALS from Claire Seyssel to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 December 12; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 417)
  - ALS from Claire Seyssel to Edward Scott-Snell, 1932 December 16; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 418)
  - ALS from Edith Sitwell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 November 16; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 419)
  - ALS from Osbert Sitwell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 October 8; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 420)
  - TLS from Osbert Sitwell to Edward Scott-Snell, 1931 November 11; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 421)
  - ALS from Honor Stamp to Edward Scott-Snell, 1935 April 9; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 422)
  - ALS from Anthony N. Stuart to Edward Scott-Snell, no year October 3; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 423)
  - ALS from Montague Summers to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 13; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 424)
  - ALS from Montague Summers to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 16; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 425)
  - ALS from Montague Summers to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 May 27; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 426)
  - ACS from Montague Summers to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 December 25; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 427)
  - ALS from Stella Sydenbam-Clarke to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 428)
  - ALS from B. Tape to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 18; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 429)
  - ALS from Kathleen Taylor to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 430)
  - ALS from Una Troubridge to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 January 20; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 431)
  - ALS from Una Troubridge to Edward Scott-Snell, 1933 February 6; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 432)
  - TLS from Roger Venables to Edward Scott-Snell, no year March 10; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 433)
  - TLS from Roger Venables to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 3 pages (Box 6, Folder 434)
  - ALS from Roger Venables to Edward Scott-Snell, undated; 1 page (Box 6, Folder 435)
  - ALS from Roger Venables to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 25; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 436)
  - TLS from Roger Venables to Edward Scott-Snell, no year June 28; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 437)